sentrals.com 2010-06-21

# Privacy Policy | Acne Care Treatment Center

**Sentrals.Com[Privacy Policy](http://sentrals.com/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy") Statement**

We are on Sentrals Network, [takes](http://sentrals.com/tag/takes "takes") your privacy seriously. [This](http://sentrals.com/tag/this "This") privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

**Routine Information Collection**  
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

**Cookies, Web Beacons and Controlling Your Privacy**  
Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. But, many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The [best](http://sentrals.com/tag/best "best") option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**Special Note About[Google](http://sentrals.com/tag/google "Google") [Advertising](http://sentrals.com/tag/advertising "Advertising")**  
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Googles cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Googles own privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to gedabrus@gmail.com for further clarification.
